<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Crstian&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Crstian&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Crstian.me © 2019.  &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io/&#34;&gt;HUGO&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:19:14 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Configure DDNS in OpenWrt Cloudflare</title>
      <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2022-01-19-openwrt-ddns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2022-01-19-openwrt-ddns/</guid>
      <description>If you have services in your home as in my case, your company will probably give you a dynamic public IP, so it is a hassle to have to be changing by hand the IP where your domain points every time your company changes the IP, so let&amp;rsquo;s see how to configure our router with OpenWRT with Cloudflare as DNS in a very simple way.
Cloudflare Token First of all we will need a cloudflare token, we can get it from here https://dash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Drone CI/CD with Traefik on NixOS</title>
      <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2021-01-15-drone-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 00:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2021-01-15-drone-ci/</guid>
      <description>In this post we are going to see how to configure our own CI/CD environment with Drone, integrated with Traefik as reverse proxy and NixOS as operating system using github repositories.
First we need to create an OAuth application in github and our RPC secret can be seen in this post or also in the drone docs.
To create our RPC secret we will do the following:
 $ openssl rand -hex 16 bea26a2221fd8090ea38720fc445eca6</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure routing for your containerized applications using Traefik v2 with Let&#39;s Encrypt</title>
      <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2020-04-19-secure-routing-for-your-containerized-applications-using-traefik-v2-with-lets-encrypt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Apr 2020 00:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2020-04-19-secure-routing-for-your-containerized-applications-using-traefik-v2-with-lets-encrypt/</guid>
      <description>Configuring traefik v2 for secure routing as reverse proxy with HTTPS
Introduction A robust reverse proxy configuration is critical for any self-hosted setup that has elements exposed across the Internet. While reverse proxy services are often used for load balancing and security reasons, most home server owners use them to route requests directed to different domains or subdomains to different hosts or internal services. In my case you can see all my services at https://server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logitech G502 Linux</title>
      <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2019-07-28-logitech-g502-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2019-07-28-logitech-g502-linux/</guid>
      <description>How to configure and use Logitech G502 on Arch Linux
How to configure and use Logitech G502 on Arch Linux After switching to Arch Linux from Windows and having a Logitech G502 I needed to configure both dpi and configurable buttons, even turn off the leds at night.
Thanks to a friend who taught me piper program made in Python which allows us to configure our G502 and more models here the list</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Github for noobies 🤔</title>
      <link>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2019-07-17-git-tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2019 00:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.crstian.me/en/post/2019-07-17-git-tutorial/</guid>
      <description>In this post we are going to see how to create our first repository and have our code ordered in Github. We are going to learn the basics and the necessary commands for it, that&amp;rsquo;s why I have titled it github for noobies or dummies like me.
Git is the most popular version control system. Git is the most popular version control system and for good reason. In this post, we will go over the basics of what git is and how to use it inside the command line.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
